

### CHRISTIANO GOMES

01.08.1991

300 Bayview Dr, Sunny Isles Beach FL

+1(305)-896-5931

christianomiami@gmail.com

https://christianogomes.netlify.app/ https://github.com/ChristianoGomes www.linkedin.com/in/christiano-Gomes



### **PROFILE**

Highly skilled and motivated Front End Developer with a passion for crafting visually stunning and user-friendly web applications. Possessing a solid foundation in web development technologies. I bring a keen eye for design and a commitment to delivering seamless and engaging user experiences.



### PROFESSIONAL CAREER

London Foster, Miami / Since July 2022 - now Realtor Sales Associate

- Managing all aspects of documentation and contracts requirements to ensure compliants with real estate regulations
- Creating and implementing effective marketing strategies to promote properties
- Building and maintaining strong client relationships through clear communication, trust-building and responsive service
- Collaborating with mortgage, brokers and inspectors to ensure an efficient closing process



### CORE COMPETENCIES

Multi-cultural with strong communication skills and good at fostering efficient team work.

I associate analytical thinking with excellent organizational and interpersonal skills. With client satisfaction as a top priority, I pride myself in the understanding and exceeding clients' expectations. I am adept at problem solving and have a proven ability to work under pressure.



#### Optimar International Realty, Sunny Isles Beach / January 2015

- July 2022

Realtor Sales Associate



- Achieved and exceeded sales targets through effective negotiation, client satisfaction and strategic business development initiatives
- Utilized a CRM systems and technology tools to organize leads, track client interactions and managed the sales process effiently



### Island House Hotel, Miami Beach / January 2012 - December 2014

- Managed front desk operations, serving as initial point of contact for

Front Desk Manager



- visitors and clients
  - Coordinated appointments, reservations and logistical support to optimize daily workflow
  - Handled administrative tasks, including data entry, filing



#### **TECHNOLOGIES**

- JavaScript
- React
- CSS
- Git & GitHub
- HTML
- Web Design
- Redux
- **Build Tools**



### **CORE ATTRIBUTES**

### **EDUCATION**

- STRUCTURED
- TEAM PLAYER
- MOTIVATED
- OPEN MINDED
- RELIABLE
- ORGANIZATIONAL
- POSITIVE
- MOTIVATOR

Front-End Engineer

Languages: JavaScript, React, Redux, CSS, Git & GitHub, HTML, Web Design, Build Tools

Codecademy / August 2022 - December 2023

FreeCodeCamp / August 2022 – December 2023 Front-End Engineer

Miami Dade College / August 2013 - July 2015

Subject: Psychology



### **LANGUAGES**

PORTUGUESE
 ENGLISH

Native language

Native language

SPANISH

Fluent



### CERTIFICATES

- Licensed Real Estate
- Front End Development Libraries
- JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures
- Responsive Web Design
- Front-End Engineer



### **INTERESTS**

Cryptocurrency, music, sports, nutrition, psychology, philosophy



# CERTIFICATE

OF COMPLETION

## Christianogomes

successfully completed the Code Foundations Skill Path



12/8/2022

Date of Issuance

July CEO



Scan to verify



# CERTIFICATE

OF COMPLETION

## Christianogomes

successfully completed the **Learn How to Code Course** 



12/6/2022

Date of Issuance

\_

Scan to verify



## freeCodeCamp(A)

This certifies that

## **Christiano Gomes**

successfully completed the

## Front End Development Libraries

Developer Certification on November 15, 2023

representing approximately 300 hours of work



**Quincy Larson** 

Executive Director, freeCodeCamp.org

Verify this certification at:

https://freecodecamp.org/certification/ChristianoGomes/front-end-development-libraries



Certificate of Completion

Christianogomes

Christianogomes

Learn JavaScript Course

Output

## freeCodeCamp(A)

This certifies that

### **Christiano Gomes**

successfully completed the

# JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures

Developer Certification on July 15, 2023

representing approximately 300, hours of work



Quincy Larson

Executive Director, freeCodeCamp.org

Verify this certification at:

https://freecodecamp.org/certification/ChristianoGomes/javascript-algorithms-and-data-structures

## freeCodeCamp(A)

This certifies that

### **Christiano Gomes**

successfully completed the

## Responsive Web Design

Developer Certification on November 16, 2023

representing approximately 300 hours of work



**Quincy Larson** 

 ${\bf Executive\ Director, free Code Camp. org}$ 

Verify this certification at:

https://free code camp.org/certification/Christiano Gomes/responsive-web-design

